Off-season training for football.
Isolated plank dog pointers.
Okay?
So this is the last exercise in our isolated series, working from the dumbbell rows to the hops to the lateral hops, forward hops, and now we are going to do plank position, and we are going to do dog pointers, which is the same exercise that we did in our previous workout, but this time we are going to do it isolated.
We are going to stick with one side, we are going to add another variability into it.
So Jonsey go ahead, pop up into your plank position.
We are going to get the elbow and the knee to touch underneath your body each time, and then get the full extension out.
So touch and full extension out.
Alright?
This is really going to put focus on shoulder stability of the off shoulder and off hip, at the same time working for balance and coordination and mobility through your torso as you are working.
So we are going to work one side of the body, and then we will work the other side of your body, and we want to follow a rep scheme of anywhere from ten reps to fifteen reps per side.
Again that is ten reps to fifteen reps per side.
For the bigger guys it is going to be a bit harder I know, but still try to stay with it.
It is really going to help with your stability and coordination and balance on the field.
And then after we finish with this exercise, when we come back and start the workouts all over again with workout one, you are going to have a lot more stability and balance to help develop more power.
So thanks a lot for joining us here, I appreciate it.
I am mike Rosengart and this is my workout partner Jonsey.
Check us out again online and have a good workout.